EEA/UK/CH

Privacy Policy

Last updated: _30 November 2025_

_We are changing how we show ads to UK users. Our new [Privacy Policy for UK users](https://www.tiktok.com/legal/page/global/privacy-policy-eea-new/en) comes into effect on 11 November 2026 or, if you are in the UK, when you make a choice about ads._

*   Introduction
*   What Information We Collect
*   How We Use Your Information
*   How We Share Your Information
*   Our Legal Bases and How We Process Your Information
*   Your Rights and Choices
*   Data Security and Retention
*   Our Global Operations and Data Transfers
*   Younger Users
*   Privacy Policy Updates
*   Contact Us

**Introduction**
----------------

This privacy policy ("**Privacy Policy**") applies to the personal information that TikTok processes in connection with TikTok apps, websites, software and related services (the “**Platform**”), that link to or reference this Privacy Policy. **Data Controller**: If you live in the European Economic Area (“**EEA**”), the United Kingdom (“**UK**”), or Switzerland, TikTok Technology Limited, an Irish company (“**TikTok Ireland**”), and TikTok Information Technologies UK Limited (“**TikTok UK**”), a UK company, ("**TikTok**," "**our**," "**we**," or "**us**") are the joint controllers of your information processed in connection with this Privacy Policy.

**What Information We Collect**
-------------------------------

We collect your information in three ways: [Information You Provide](#info-you-provide), [Automatically Collected Information](#auto-collect-info), and [Information From Other Sources](#info-from-other). More detail is provided below.

### **Information You Provide**

*   **Account Information.** We collect information that you provide when you set up an account, such as your date of birth, username, email address and/or telephone number, and password. You can choose to add other information to your account, such as a bio or image.
*   **User Content.** We collect the content you create, import, upload or publish through the Platform, such as photographs, videos, audio recordings, livestreams, comments, hashtags, feedback, reviews, and the associated metadata (such as when, where, and by whom the content was created). Even if you are not a user, information about you may appear in content created or published by users on the Platform. We collect [User Content](#user-content) through pre-loading at the time of creation, import, or upload, regardless of whether you choose to save or upload that [User Content](#user-content), for example, to recommend music based on the video. We also collect content (such as text, images, and video) from your device's clipboard if you choose to copy and paste content to or from the Platform or share content between it and a third party platform. In addition, we collect location information (such as tourist attractions, shops, or other points of interest) if you choose to add the location information to your [User Content](#user-content).
*   **Messages.** We collect the content of the messages you send and receive on the Platform and the associated metadata (such as the time the message was sent, received or read, as well as the participants in the communication). We also collect the messages you send or receive through our chat functionality when using our shopping feature to communicate with sellers or using virtual assistants.
*   **Your Contacts and Other Connections.** If you choose to sync your contacts, we will collect information from your device’s phone book such as names, phone numbers, and email addresses, and match that information to users of the Platform. If you choose to find other users through your social network contacts, we will collect your public profile information as well as names and profiles of your social network contacts. We also collect information about the accounts you follow and that follow you.
*   **Purchase Information.** When you make a purchase, a payment, or other transaction on or through the Platform, including when you buy TikTok Coins or purchase products through our shopping features, we collect information about the transaction, such as payment card information, billing, delivery, and contact information, and products you purchased.
*   **Surveys, Research, and Promotions.** We collect [Information You Provide](#info-you-provide) if you choose to participate in a survey, research, promotion, contest, marketing campaign, or event conducted or sponsored by us.
*   **Information When You Contact Us.** When you contact us, we collect the information you send us, such as proof of identity or age, feedback or inquiries about your use of the Platform or information about possible violations of our [Terms of Service](https://www.tiktok.com/legal/terms-of-service) (our “**Terms**”), [Community Guidelines](https://www.tiktok.com/community-guidelines) (our “**Guidelines**”), or other policies.
*   **Information From Forms and Features You Use**. We collect the [Information You Provide](#info-you-provide) when you fill in a form on the Platform. You can let TikTok fill in forms automatically with your account info, like your addresses or payment info.

### **Automatically Collected Information**

*   **Technical Information.** We collect certain device and network connection information when you access the Platform. This information includes your device model, operating system, keystroke patterns or rhythms, IP address, system language and device settings. We also collect service-related, diagnostic, performance information, including crash reports and performance logs. We automatically assign you a device ID and user ID. Where you log-in from multiple devices, we use information such as your device ID and user ID to identify your activity across devices to give you a seamless log-in experience and for security purposes.
*   **Location Information.** We automatically collect information about your approximate location (e.g. country, state, or city) based on your [Technical Information](#tech-info) (such as SIM card and IP address). Also, where you enable location services for the TikTok app within your device settings, we collect approximate or precise location information from your device. Click [here](https://support.tiktok.com/en/account-and-privacy/account-privacy-settings/location-services-on-tiktok) to learn more about how we collect Location Information.
*   **Usage Information.** We collect information about how you engage with the Platform, including information about how you interact with content and ads, the duration and frequency of your use, your engagement with other users, and your search history. _We also collect information about your interactions with websites when you use our in-app browser._
*   **Content Characteristics and Features.** We detect and collect characteristics and features about the videos, images, and audio recordings that are part of your [User Content](#user-content), for example, by identifying objects and scenery, the existence or location within an image of a face or other body parts; and the text of words spoken in your [User Content](#user-content). We do this, for example, for content moderation and to provide special effects (such as video filters and avatars) and captions.
*   **Inferred Information.** We infer your attributes (such as age-range and gender) and interests based on the information we have about you. We use inferences, for example, to keep the Platform safe (such as for content moderation), to show you relevant information, and, where permitted, to serve you personalised ads based on your interests.
*   **Cookies.** We use cookies and similar tracking technologies to operate and provide the Platform. For example, we use cookies to remember your language preferences, make sure you don’t see the same video more than once, and for security purposes. We also use these technologies for marketing purposes. To learn more about our use of cookies, please see our [Cookies Policy](https://www.tiktok.com/legal/tiktok-website-cookies-policy). We will obtain your consent to our use of cookies where required by law.

### **Information From Other Sources**

*   **Advertising, Measurement and Other Partners.** Advertisers, measurement and other partners share information with us about you and the actions you have taken outside of the Platform, such as your activities on other websites and apps or in stores, including the products or services you purchased, online or in person. These partners also share information with us, such as mobile identifiers for advertising, hashed email addresses and phone numbers, and cookie identifiers, which we use to help match you and your actions outside of the Platform with your TikTok account. Some of our advertisers and other partners enable us to collect similar information directly from their website or app by integrating our [TikTok Advertiser Tools](https://ads.tiktok.com/help/article?aid=10000407) (such as TikTok Pixel). These partners are required to have the necessary rights and permissions to share your information with us before doing so. We process certain information that we receive from these partners as a joint controller with them. [Learn more](https://ads.tiktok.com/i18n/official/policy/business-products-terms) about our arrangements with these partners.
*   **Sellers, Payment and Transaction Fulfillment Providers.** We receive information about you from sellers as well as payment and transaction fulfillment providers, such as payment confirmation details, and information about the delivery of products you have purchased through our shopping features.
*   **Third Party Platforms and Partners.** Third party platforms provide us with information (such as your email address, authentication ID, and public profile) when you choose to sign up for or log in to the Platform using sign-in features provided by those third parties. We may also receive contact information that you hold or is held about you when contact information is synced with our Platform by you or another user. When you interact with any third party service (such as third party apps, websites or products) that integrate [TikTok Developer Tools](https://developers.tiktok.com/), we will receive the information necessary to provide you with features like cross-service authentication or cross-posting. For example, this will happen if you log in to another platform with your TikTok account or if you use TikTok’s “share” button on a third party platform to share content from there to the Platform. We may also receive information from third party providers which we use for safety purposes, including to protect users on the Platform and for content moderation.
*   **Additional Sources.** We may collect or receive information about you from organisations, businesses, people, and others, including, for example, publicly available sources, government authorities, professional organisations, and charity groups. We also collect information about you where you are included or mentioned in [User Content](#user-content), [Messages](#message), in a complaint, appeal, request or feedback submitted by a user or third party, or if your contact information is provided to us by a user.

**How We Use Your Information**
-------------------------------

We use your information to operate, provide, develop, and improve the Platform, including for the following purposes. You can find more detail in “[Our Legal Bases and How We Process Your Information](#legal-base)”.

*   Provide and administer the Platform, such as enabling you to create, share, and consume content, to interact with other users and their content, and provide user support.
*   Provide our shopping features (such as personalised shopping benefits) and facilitate the purchase and delivery of products, goods and services, including sharing your information with sellers, payment and transaction fulfilment providers, and other service providers in order to process your orders.
*   Personalise and customise certain features and content such as providing your “For You” feed and content creation tools.
*   Enforce our Terms, Guidelines, and other policies that apply to you. We review [User Content](#user-content) and other information through a mix of technology (including through automated means) and human moderation to protect the safety and well-being of our community.
*   Provide certain interactive features, such as enabling your content to be used in other users’ videos,
*   Suggest your account to other users and suggest accounts of others to you to help connect you with other users.
*   Provide and improve our advertising services, including to serve ads (including personalised ads, where permitted). For information about how we process personal information through our advertising network, see our [TikTok Ad Network Privacy Policy](https://www.tiktok.com/legal/tiktok-ad-network-privacy-policy).
*   Create analytics reports so that partners, sellers and creators can see how their content, ads or products are performing and to better understand their audience and buyers.
*   Maintain and enhance the safety, security, and stability of the Platform by identifying and addressing technical or security issues or problems (such as technical bugs, spam accounts, and detecting abuse, fraud, and illegal activity).
*   Review, improve, and develop the Platform, including by monitoring interactions and usage across your devices, analysing how people are using it, and by training, testing, and improving our technology, such as our machine learning models and algorithms.
*   Share your information with third party platforms to provide you with features, like content sharing at your request when you integrate your TikTok account with a third party service.
*   Facilitate research conducted by independent researchers that meets certain criteria.
*   Promote the Platform or third party services through marketing communications, contests, or promotions.
*   Facilitate the sending of marketing communications by sellers to you on our Platform. We act as a joint controller with the sellers in this scenario. [Learn more](https://seller-uk.tiktok.com/university/essay?role=1&knowledge_id=2762929708418849&from=other&article_type=agreement&identity=1) about our arrangements with these sellers.
*   Comply with our legal obligations, or as necessary to perform tasks in the public interest, or to protect the vital interests of our users and other people.
*   Protect the Platform and defend our legal rights and commercial interests, and those of our affiliates, users and the public.

**How We Share Your Information**
---------------------------------

### **Service Providers**

We engage service providers that help us provide, support, and develop the Platform and understand how it is used. They provide services such as: cloud hosting, and content delivery, customer and technical support, content moderation, marketing, analytics, and payment services.

We share [Information You Provide](#info-you-provide), [Automatically Collected Information](#auto-collect-info), and [Information From Other Sources](#info-from-other) with these service providers as necessary to enable them to provide their services.

### **Partners**

**Third Party Platforms and Partners.** We share limited information which may include [Information You Provide](#info-you-provide), [Technical Information](#tech-info), and [Usage Information](#usage-info) with third party platforms and partners whose platform or services are integrated with the Platform, or with whom we have a commercial relationship. We do this to give you a seamless experience, allow your content to be shared on other platforms, allow sellers to view and manage your orders through our shopping features, and enable third party platforms and partners to better authenticate users. Some examples include if you:

*   log-in to a third party platform using your account, we will share your basic account information and any other [Information You Provide](#info-you-provide),
*   sign-up or log-in to the Platform using your account details from a third party platform (such as Facebook or Google), we will share certain [Technical Information](#tech-info) to facilitate this,
*   share [User Content](#user-content) you publish on the Platform on other social media platforms, we will share your [User Content](#user-content) and related information.

**Advertisers.** We provide advertisers with reports about the performance of their ads and other content on the Platform in order to help them measure their effectiveness and understand their audience. These reports contain aggregate information of certain [Information You Provide](#info-you-provide), [Automatically Collected Information](#auto-collect-info), and [Information From Other Sources](#info-from-other). We don’t share information with advertisers that can be used to contact you (such as your name or email address) unless you give us your permission.

**Measurement and Data Partners.** We share [Information You Provide](#info-you-provide), [Technical Information](#tech-info) and [Usage Information](#usage-info) with third party measurement providers who create aggregate reports that help us measure advertising served on the Platform and help our advertisers understand their effectiveness and their audience.

**Sellers and their Service Providers.** When you make a purchase through the shopping features on our Platform, we share [Purchase Information](#purchase-info) related to the transaction with the sellers and service providers acting on their behalf. This includes order items, contact details and delivery information so that your order can be processed. We also share certain [Technical Information](#tech-info) about your device or connection with these parties to help ensure the security of the transaction. When making a purchase through our shopping features, please review the product and seller location details provided on the Platform for information about where your information will be sent.

**Users of Our Analytics Services.** We provide aggregated statistics and insights to help people and businesses understand how people are engaging with the Platform. For example, creators, advertisers and sellers can receive information about the number of views, likes, comments and shares of their content, as well as information to understand their followers, buyers and the audience of their content. We create this aggregate information using [Information You Provide](#info-you-provide) and [Automatically Collected Information](#auto-collect-info). In certain circumstances, TikTok is a joint controller with TikTok account holders for this processing. [Learn more](https://www.tiktok.com/legal/page/global/information-about-tiktok-analytics/en) about the joint processing for TikTok Analytics.

### **Our Corporate Group**

As a global company, the Platform is supported by certain entities within our corporate group (“**Corporate Group**”). These entities process [Information You Provide](#info-you-provide), [Automatically Collected Information](#auto-collect-info), and [Information From Other Sources](#info-from-other) for us, as necessary to provide certain functions, such as storage, content delivery, security, research and development, analytics, payment services, customer and technical support, and content moderation. See [Our Global Operations and Data Transfers](#global-ops-data-transfers) for additional information.

### **Others**

We share your information in other limited scenarios as follows:

**Users and the Public.** Based on your privacy settings, your information, including your [Account Information](#account-info), [User Content](#user-content), and [Usage Information](#usage-info) may be visible to other users and the public. For example, if you have a public account and have not restricted the visibility of your posts individually, your [Account Information](#account-info) and [User Content](#user-content) can be viewed or shared by anyone on or off the Platform, whether or not they have a TikTok account. Depending on your privacy settings, your [Account Information](#account-info) and [User Content](#user-content) may also appear on search engines, content aggregators, and news sites. You can learn about account types and privacy settings, including how to limit the audience for your videos [here](https://support.tiktok.com/en/account-and-privacy/account-privacy-settings).

**Independent Researchers:** We share your information with independent researchers to facilitate research that meets certain criteria as described in [Our Legal Bases and How We Process Your Information](#legal-base).

**Corporate Transactions.** Your information may be disclosed to third parties in connection with a corporate transaction, such as a merger, sale of assets or shares, reorganisation, financing, change of control, or acquisition of all or a portion of our business.

**Legal Obligations and Rights.** We may access, preserve, and share the information described in "[What Information We Collect](#info-collected)" with law enforcement agencies, public authorities, researchers, copyright holders, or other third parties if we have good faith belief that it is necessary to:

*   comply with applicable law, legal process or government requests, as consistent with internationally recognised standards,
*   protect the rights, property, and safety of our users, copyright holders, and others, including to protect life or prevent imminent bodily harm. For example, we may provide information (such as your IP address) to law enforcement in the event of an emergency where someone’s life or safety is at risk,
*   investigate potential violations of and enforce our Terms, Guidelines, or any other applicable terms, policies, or standards, or
*   detect, investigate, prevent, or address misleading activity, copyright infringement, or other illegal activity.

To learn more about how we handle requests from law enforcement agencies and public authorities, see our [Law Enforcement Guidelines](https://www.tiktok.com/legal/law-enforcement).

**Our Legal Bases and How We Process Your Information**
-------------------------------------------------------

We may only use your information when we have a “legal basis” to do so. We use different legal bases depending on why we use your information (in other words, the “purpose” of our processing). These legal bases are contractual necessity, legitimate interests (ours, yours or those of another party), consent, compliance with a legal obligation, performing a task in the public interest, and protection of vital interests.

Here we explain the legal bases we rely on when we process your information. This section also describes why we use your information, how this information is processed, the categories of information involved, and the associated rights (which always includes the right to access your information). For more information on how to exercise any of your rights, please check out the “[Your Rights and Choices](#your-rights)” section in the Privacy Policy.

### **Contractual Necessity**

If you have the legal capacity to enter into an enforceable contract, we use [Information You Provide](#info-you-provide), [Automatically Collected Information](#auto-collect-info), and [Information From Other Sources](#info-from-other) where it is necessary to perform the contract you enter into (our Terms) when you register for, access, or use the Platform. This means we use your information to:

*   **Provide you with the Platform.** We use your information to allow you to access and use the Platform, including allowing you to create, share and consume content, interact with others, utilise social features, and provide you with products and services you purchase.
*   **Personalise features and content.** We also personalise certain features and content such as providing your “For You” feed, which shows you videos that we think you would be interested in (see [here](https://support.tiktok.com/en/using-tiktok/exploring-videos/for-you) for more information) and by suggesting accounts to you.
*   **Product orders and deliveries.** We use your information to process orders, such as to facilitate the purchase and delivery of products, and communicate with you about your orders. This includes sharing [Purchase Information](#purchase-info) with Sellers, Payment and Transaction Fulfilment Providers, and Other Service Providers
*   **Enforce our Terms, Guidelines, or policies.** We use your information to enforce our Terms, Guidelines, and policies (including through automated means and human moderation). This may include age restricting or removing content, maintaining our For You feed eligibility standards, or suspending or banning your account if we determine that you are violating our Terms or Guidelines.
*   **Administer the Platform.** We also use the information we have to administer the Platform, such as to communicate with you on service related matters, provide you with updates and support regarding any purchase you make on or through the Platform, and respond to and process your queries, claims or disputes (including when you tell us about a problem, or ask for a copy of your information).

**Your Rights**: Whenever we use your information on the basis that it is necessary for the contract we have with you, you have the right to port information you have provided to us.

### **Legitimate Interests**

We use your information where this is necessary to achieve legitimate interests - whether belonging to us, you, or a third party - provided these interests are not outweighed by your interests or fundamental rights and freedoms. We use the information we collect to:

**Enable users to create content with interactive features**.

*   Interactive features, like Duet and Stitch, enable other users to include your videos in their videos (if you allow this in your settings).
*   **Legitimate Interest relied upon**: To provide users with tools to inspire creativity, collaboration, and enjoyment, and to create opportunities for users to reach new audiences.
*   **Information used**: [Information You Provide](#info-you-provide) and [Automatically Collected Information](#auto-collect-info).

**Suggest your account to other users**.

*   We may suggest your account to other users, including when a user chooses to sync their contacts with the Platform.
*   **Legitimate Interest relied upon**: To enable users to quickly and efficiently find and connect with other users.
*   **Information used**: [Information You Provide](#info-you-provide), [Automatically Collected Information](#auto-collect-info), and [Information From Other Sources](#info-from-other).

**Provide all users with generic advertising**.

*   We show all users generic ads, including those who have chosen not to receive personalised ads.
*   **Legitimate Interest relied upon**: We show generic ads to keep the Platform free of charge. We process limited categories of your information to make sure our advertising service is useful to our advertisers (for example, to serve ads to users in a particular country or to users who speak the same language).
*   **Information used**: [Information You Provide](#info-you-provide) and [Automatically Collected Information](#auto-collect-info).

**Provide measurement and analytics services**.

*   We help creators, sellers and advertisers measure the effectiveness and distribution of ads and other content viewed on the Platform.
*   **Legitimate Interest relied upon**: To enable creators, sellers and advertisers to view and understand how their ads or content performed and the audience that viewed or interacted with their ads or content. This is so that they can make informed decisions (such as what kinds of ad campaigns they may want to run, the type of audience they want to reach and the types of content that users enjoy the most). This helps keep the advertising and other content we show users relevant and entertaining, and keeps the Platform free for all users.
*   **Information used**: [Information You Provide](#info-you-provide), [Automatically Collected Information](#auto-collect-info), and [Information From Other Sources](#info-from-other).

**Ensure the safety and well-being of our community**.

*   We use your information to ensure the safety and well-being of our community, including by reviewing [User Content](#user-content) (and if permitted under applicable law, [Messages](#message) and associated metadata) for breaches of our Terms, Guidelines, and other policies. We also infer your age range, and under certain circumstances, may ask you to provide additional information to confirm your age.
*   **Legitimate Interest relied upon**: To keep our community safe, review compliance with our Guidelines, and identify misuse of the Platform.
*   **Information used**: [Information You Provide](#info-you-provide), [Automatically Collected Information](#auto-collect-info), and [Information From Other Sources](#info-from-other).

**Ensure the security and stability of the Platform**.

*   We use your information to ensure the stability and security of the Platform, including by identifying and combating technical or security issues (such as technical bugs, spam accounts, and detecting abuse, fraud, and illegal activity).
*   **Legitimate Interest relied upon**: To ensure the ongoing stability and security of the Platform and to ensure it is continuously available and functioning.
*   **Information used**: [Information You Provide](#info-you-provide), [Automatically Collected Information](#auto-collect-info), and [Information From Other Sources](#info-from-other).

**Review, improve, promote, and develop the Platform**.

*   We use the information we have to understand how people are using the Platform and to develop, test, and make improvements to the Platform, including to develop and improve our technology, such as our machine learning models and algorithms. We also use this information to better understand and promote the Platform, popular topics, and emerging trends, and offer certain personalised features. We also review messages you exchange with customer support to improve technologies supporting such functions.
*   **Legitimate Interest relied upon**: To improve, promote, and develop the Platform in an informed way.
*   **Information used**: [Information You Provide](#info-you-provide\), [Automatically Collected Information](#auto-collect-info), and [Information From Other Sources](#info-from-other).

**Facilitate independent research.**

*   We share your information with independent researchers to facilitate research that meets certain criteria, including where such researchers have demonstrable experience and expertise in their area. Click [here](https://developers.tiktok.com/doc/about-research-api/) to learn more
*   **Legitimate Interest relied upon**: To facilitate independent research that aims to develop society’s collective knowledge, including in the areas of misinformation and disinformation, violence, cybercrime, and social trends.
*   **Information used**: [Information You Provide](#info-you-provide), [Automatically Collected Information](#auto-collect-info)**.**

**Share your information with third parties**.

*   We share your information with third parties whose platforms or services are integrated with, or otherwise made available on, the Platform.
*   **Legitimate Interest relied upon**: To optimise your experience, allow your content to be shared on other platforms, enable third parties to authenticate users, and to allow for the performance of commercial agreements.
*   **Information used**: [Information You Provide](#info-you-provide), [Automatically Collected Information](#auto-collect-info), and [Information From Other Sources](#info-from-other).

**Protect the Platform and defend legal rights**

*   We may use your information in connection with preparing for, taking and defending actual or anticipated legal claims or proceedings (including investigating any potential claims we may have or be aware of).
*   **Legitimate Interest relied upon**: to protect the Platform and defend the legal rights and commercial interests of us, our affiliates, our users and the public.
*   **Information used**: [Information You Provide](#info-you-provide), [Automatically Collected Information](#auto-collect-info), and [Information From Other Sources](#info-from-other).

**Marketing communications**.

*   You may receive marketing messages about the Platform and third party products and services where we think they will interest you. Where required, we will obtain your consent to send you such communications.
*   **Legitimate Interest relied upon**: To promote the Platform and third party products and services.
*   **Information used**: [Information You Provide](#info-you-provide), [Automatically Collected Information](#auto-collect-info), and [Information From Other Sources](#info-from-other).

**Your Rights**: Whenever we use your information on the basis that it is necessary for legitimate interests, you can object to, and request restriction of, such usage.

**If you are under the age of majority (under 18 in most relevant countries), with a limited ability to enter into an enforceable contract only, where we may be unable to process your information on the grounds of contractual necessity, we rely on legitimate interests and use the information we collect to:**

**Provide you with the Platform**

*   We use your information to allow you to access and use the Platform, including allowing you to create, share, and consume content, interact with others, utilise features, and provide you with products and services you purchase.
*   **Legitimate Interests relied upon**: To provide, support, and maintain products and features that enable users who can’t enter into an enforceable contract with us to communicate, discover, and engage with content and express themselves. We also rely on the legitimate interest of our users in being able to access the Platform in an easy and intuitive manner..
*   **Information used**: [Information You Provide](#info-you-provide), [Automatically Collected Information](#auto-collect-info), and [Information From Other Sources](#info-from-other).

**Personalise features and content**

*   We use your information to personalise certain features and content on the Platform, such as providing your “For You” feed, which shows you videos that we think you would be interested in (see [here](https://support.tiktok.com/en/using-tiktok/exploring-videos/for-you) for more information) and by suggesting accounts to you.
*   **Legitimate Interests relied upon**: To provide, support, and maintain products and features that enable users who can’t enter into an enforceable contract with us to communicate, discover, create and engage with content and users relevant to their interests. We also rely on the legitimate interest of our users who can’t enter into an enforceable contract with us in being able to access the Platform and content relevant to their interests.
*   **Information used**: [Information You Provide](#info-you-provide), [Automatically Collected Information](#auto-collect-info), and [Information From Other Sources](#info-from-other).

**Enforce our Terms, Guidelines, or policies.**

*   We use your information to enforce our Terms, Guidelines, and policies (including through automated means and human moderation). This may include age restricting or removing content, maintaining our For You feed eligibility standards, or suspending or banning your account if we determine that you are violating our Terms or Guidelines.
*   **Legitimate Interests relied upon**: To keep the Platform free of harmful or inappropriate content, to investigate suspicious activity or breaches of our Terms, Guidelines, or policies and to protect the safety of users who can’t enter into an enforceable contract with us, including to prevent exploitation or other harm to which such individuals may be particularly vulnerable. It is also in the legitimate interests of our users who can’t enter into an enforceable contract with us, and the public at large, to prevent bad experiences and promote safety, integrity and security.
*   **Information used**: [Information You Provide](#info-you-provide), [Automatically Collected Information](#auto-collect-info), and [Information From Other Sources](#info-from-other).

**Administer the Platform.**

*   We use the information we have to administer the Platform, such as to communicate with users and respond to and process queries, claims or disputes (including when you tell us about a problem, or ask for a copy of your information).
*   **Legitimate Interests relied upon**: To share meaningful updates with our users who can’t enter into an enforceable contract with us about service-related matters, and process their queries, claims and disputes.
*   **Information used**: [Information You Provide](#info-you-provide), [Automatically Collected Information](#auto-collect-info), and [Information From Other Sources](#info-from-other).

**Your Rights**: Whenever we use your information on the basis that it is necessary for legitimate interests, you can object to, and request restriction of, such usage.

### **Your Consent**

We ask for your consent to access or use your information for specific purposes. If we do, you’ll always be able to revoke your consent through your device permissions or in-app settings.

**Personalised advertising**.

*   With your consent, we serve you personalised ads on the Platform based on your activity on and off the Platform. Click [here](https://www.tiktok.com/safety/en/ads-and-data/) to learn more.
*   With your consent and in regions where it is available, we use certain information associated with your TikTok user account to personalise ads served via our advertising network. For more information see the [TikTok Ad Network Privacy Policy](https://www.tiktok.com/legal/tiktok-ad-network-privacy-policy).
*   **Information used**: [Information You Provide](#info-you-provide), [Automatically Collected Information](#auto-collect-info), and [Information From Other Sources](#info-from-other) for this purpose.

**Retain your payment card information.**

*   With your consent, we store your payment card information to facilitate future transactions through our Platform.
*   **Information used:** [Information You Provide](#info-you-provide)

**Sellers’ marketing communications.**

*   With your consent, we facilitate the sending of marketing communications to you by sellers on our Platform and/or share your email address with sellers for the purpose of sending marketing communications to you.
*   **Information used:** [Information You Provide](#info-you-provide) and [Automatically Collected Information](#auto-collect-info),

**Device permissions.**

*   We collect information that you allow us to receive through your device-based settings (such as access to your camera, photos and location services) which we use for subsequent purposes as described in this Privacy Policy.
*   **Information used:** [Information You Provide](#info-you-provide), [Automatically Collected Information](#auto-collect-info), and [Information From Other Sources](#info-from-other)

**Your rights**: Whenever we use your information based on your consent, you can withdraw your consent at any time. However, your withdrawal of consent will not affect the lawfulness of processing your information based on your consent prior to your withdrawal of consent. You can withdraw your consent for applicable personalised ads related settings by following these [instructions](https://support.tiktok.com/en/account-and-privacy/personalized-ads-and-data/personalization-and-data).

You also have the right to port information you have provided to us that we use based on your consent.

### **Compliance with a legal obligation**

We may use your information including your [Account Information](#account-info) or [User Content](#user-content) where it is necessary to comply with a legal obligation. This includes situations where we have obligations to communicate with you, take measures to ensure the safety of our users, or comply with a valid legal request such as an order or disclosure request from regulators, law enforcement agencies or courts. We generally use [Information You Provide](#info-you-provide) and [Automatically Collected Information](#auto-collect-info), although it depends on the specific situation.

### **To perform a task in the public interest**

We may use your information where it is necessary to perform a task in the public interest, including undertaking research, preventing and detecting crime, safeguarding children and promoting public safety, security, and integrity as laid down by applicable law. We generally use [Information You Provide](#info-you-provide) and [Automatically Collected Information](#auto-collect-info), although it depends on the specific situation.

**Your rights**: When we use your information on the basis that it is necessary for a task carried out in the public interest, you have the right to object to, and seek restriction of, our usage.

### **To protect someone's vital interests**

We may use your information where it is necessary to protect your or someone else's life, physical integrity, or safety. This could include scanning [Messages](#message) and associated metadata where permitted by law. Click [here](https://support.tiktok.com/en/account-and-privacy/account-privacy-settings/direct-message) to learn more. This could also include providing law enforcement agencies or emergency services with information in urgent situations to protect health or life. We generally provide [Information You Provide](#info-you-provide) and [Automatically Collected Information](#auto-collect-info), although it depends on the specific situation.

**Your Rights and Choices**
---------------------------

You have rights and choices when it comes to your information. Some of these rights apply generally, while others will only apply in certain circumstances. Depending on the scenario, these rights may be subject to some limitations. TikTok Ireland will be responsible for responding to your request within the relevant periods provided by law. If necessary to resolve your request, TikTok Ireland will liaise with TikTok UK.

**Access your information.** You can ask us, free of charge, to confirm what information we process about you, to provide certain information about the processing, and for a copy of your information. In-app controls enable you to:

*   access your information that is available to other users when you navigate to the "**me**" tab on your account.
*   request a copy of your information by using the “**Download your data**” tool. Click [here](https://support.tiktok.com/en/account-and-privacy/personalized-ads-and-data/requesting-your-data) for detailed instructions.

**Delete your information.** You can delete or ask us to delete your information. In-app controls enable you to:

*   delete the content posted on your account, such as your [User Content](#user-content) and your [Account Information](#account-info).
*   delete your full account. Click [here](https://support.tiktok.com/en/account-and-privacy/deleting-an-account) for detailed instructions.
*   request the deletion of a particular piece of content using the in-app reporting feature (more information is available [here](https://support.tiktok.com/en/safety-hc/report-a-problem)).

**Rectify your information.** You can change or ask us to change or correct your information where that information is not accurate. You can change or correct much of your information through the in-app controls and settings (such as your [Account Information](#account-info) and video content).

**Port your information.** You have the right to data portability in circumstances where we rely on contractual necessity or consent as our legal basis. This means that you have the right to receive your information in a structured, commonly used, and machine-readable format and to share it with a third party. You can exercise your right of portability by choosing to “**Download your data**” in your settings. Click [here](https://support.tiktok.com/en/account-and-privacy/personalized-ads-and-data/requesting-your-data) for detailed instructions. You can also port your TikTok data through TikTok’s Data Portability API. Click [here](https://developers.tiktok.com/products/data-portability-api/) for further information.

**Object to the processing of your information**. You also have the [right to object](https://www.tiktok.com/legal/right-to-object?lang=en) to the processing of your information in certain circumstances. This right applies when we are performing a task in the public interest, pursuing our legitimate interests or those of a third party, or when your data is processed for the purpose of facilitating scientific or historical research in certain circumstances. In submitting an objection request, please provide all relevant information, including the processing activity you are objecting to, why you want to object and how the processing activity affects you, and any additional information that you think will help us review your request. We will stop the particular processing if we don't have compelling legitimate grounds to continue that processing or don’t need it for legal claims.

**Restrict the processing of your information**. You have the right to request the restriction of the processing of your information where (a) you are challenging the accuracy of the information, (b) the information has been unlawfully processed, but you are opposing the deletion of that information, (c) where you need the information to be retained for the pursuit or defence of a legal claim, or (d) you have objected to processing and you are awaiting the outcome of that objection request.

To exercise any of the above rights, please contact us through our [webform](https://www.tiktok.com/legal/report/privacy). Before we can respond to a request to exercise one or more of the rights listed above, you may be required to verify your identity or your account details or provide additional information so that we can understand your request.

We encourage you to “[Contact us](#contact-us)” if you are not satisfied with how we have responded to any of your rights requests. You also have the right to lodge a complaint with the Irish Data Protection Commission (TikTok Ireland’s lead supervisory authority) or with your local supervisory authority.

In addition to these rights, you can control privacy settings for your account. Click [here](https://support.tiktok.com/en/account-and-privacy/account-privacy-settings) for more information.

**Your choice regarding the use of information across different services.**

_If you are a user in the EU, we offer you the choice of whether to combine and cross-use your TikTok activity data with our affiliated services, like TikTok Shop, where legally required. [Learn more](https://www.tiktok.com/legal/page/global/tiktok-shop-dma/en)_.

**Data Security and Retention**
-------------------------------

Security of your information is important to us. We maintain appropriate technical, administrative, and physical security measures that are designed to protect your information from unauthorised access, theft, disclosure, modification, or loss. We regularly review our security measures to consider available new technology and methods.

We retain information for as long as necessary to provide the Platform and for the other purposes set out in this Privacy Policy. We also retain information when necessary to comply with contractual and legal obligations, when we have a legitimate business interest to do so (such as improving and developing the Platform, and enhancing its safety, security and stability), and for the exercise or defence of legal claims.

The retention periods will be different depending on the type of information and the purposes for which we use the information. For example, when we process your information to provide you with the Platform, we keep this information for as long as you have an account. This information includes your [Account Information](#account-info), [User Content](#user-content), and [Messages](#message). If you violate our Guidelines or Terms, we may remove [Information You Provide](#info-you-provide) including your [Account Information](#account-info) and/or [User Content](#user-content) from public view immediately but keep your information as is necessary to process the violation.

**Our Global Operations and Data Transfers**
--------------------------------------------

To support our global operations:

*   We store the information described in the “[What Information We Collect](#info-collected)” section in servers located in the United States, Malaysia and Singapore.
*   Certain entities in our Corporate Group, located outside your country of residence (see [here](https://www.tiktok.com/legal/page/eea/transferee-countries/en)), are given limited remote access to this information so they can provide certain functions, as described in the Our Corporate Group section in “[How We Share Your Information](#share-info)”. This access is limited, secure and only granted where necessary under strict security controls and authorisation approval protocols.
*   We share “[What Information We Collect](#info-collected)” with service providers, partners and other third party entities, as described in “[How We Share Your Information](#share-info)”. These third parties can be located outside your country of residence.

These entities commit to processing information in compliance with applicable privacy laws and to implementing appropriate security measures to protect your information.

When we transfer your information outside of the EEA, the UK, or Switzerland, we ensure it benefits from an adequate level of data protection by relying on:

*   Adequacy decisions. These are decisions from the [European Commission](https://ec.europa.eu/info/law/law-topic/data-protection/international-dimension-data-protection/adequacy-decisions_en) under Article 45 GDPR (or equivalent decisions under other laws) where they recognise that a country offers an adequate level of data protection. We transfer your information as described in “[What Information We Collect](#info-collected)” to some countries with adequacy decisions, such as the countries listed [here](https://www.tiktok.com/legal/page/eea/transferee-countries/en); or
*   Article 49. In the absence of an adequacy decision, We rely on Article 49 (1)(b) and (c) GDPR to transfer [Purchase Information](https://bytedance.sg.larkoffice.com/docx/IABcdmCZGoOq4WxMgHQlH1CBgQd#share-RrVCdnNjYoFcTOxgVDqljZFSg4b) as described in “[What Information We Collect](#info-collected)” to sellers and transaction fulfilment providers in countries without an adequacy decision when necessary to provide shopping features to facilitate the purchase and delivery of products, goods and services, or to process your orders; or
*   Standard contractual clauses. The European Commission has approved [contractual clauses](https://commission.europa.eu/document/download/e60b1cd4-d802-44d5-9cac-ddd3c943a5ef_en?filename=1_en_annexe_acte_autonome_cp_part1_v5_0.pdf) under Article 46 of the GDPR that allows companies in the EEA to transfer data outside the EEA. These (and their approved equivalent for the UK and Switzerland) are called standard contractual clauses. We rely on standard contractual clauses to transfer information as described in “[What Information We Collect](#info-collected)” to certain entities in our Corporate Group (as described [here](https://www.tiktok.com/legal/page/eea/transferee-countries/en)) and third parties in countries without an adequacy decision.

For a copy of these adequacy decisions or standard contractual clauses, please contact us via the details provided in the “[Contact us](#contact-us)” section below.

**Younger Users**
-----------------

You must be at least 13 years old to use the Platform. If you believe that there is a user who is below this minimum age, please contact us using this [webform](https://support.tiktok.com/en/safety-hc/report-a-problem/report-underage-accounts-on-tiktok).

To provide users younger than 18 with an age-appropriate experience, certain features are not available. Further details are available in our [Help Centre](https://support.tiktok.com/en/account-and-privacy/account-privacy-settings/privacy-and-safety-settings-for-users-under-age-18).

If you are the guardian of a teen, our [Guardian's Guide](https://www.tiktok.com/safety/en-us/guardians-guide/) contains information and resources to help you understand the Platform and the tools and controls you or your teen can use, including “Family Pairing” features.

**Privacy Policy Updates**
--------------------------

We may amend or update this Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify you of any material changes to this policy by a notice provided through the Platform or by other means. The “Last Updated” date at the top of this policy reflects the effective date of such policy changes.

**Contact Us**
--------------

You can contact us about this Privacy Policy through our [webform](https://www.tiktok.com/legal/report/privacy). You can reach TikTok's Data Protection Officer [here](https://www.tiktok.com/legal/report/DPO).

You can also contact us at the following postal address.

*   **For users in the European Economic Area and Switzerland**: TikTok Technology Limited, 10 Earlsfort Terrace, Dublin, D02 T380, Ireland.
*   **For users in Switzerland, our appointed representative is:** TikTok Switzerland GmbH, Talacker 41, 8001, Zürich, Switzerland.
*   **For users in the United Kingdom**: TikTok Information Technologies UK Limited, Kaleidoscope, 4 Lindsey Street, London, EC1A 9HP, United Kingdom.

- - -

Children's Privacy Policy

*   For Children
*   For Parents, Guardians, and Other Adults

_Last updated: January 22, 2026_

**_For Children_**
------------------

TikTok cares about your privacy. Children under the age of 13 in the United States can use TikTok in the Under 13 Experience. When you use the Under 13 Experience, we collect some information from you. This page explains what information we get and how we use it.

### **What Information Do We Collect from You?**

When you use TikTok, we collect some information about you. For example, when you set up a TikTok account, we collect your birthday, username, and password. We also collect some information from your phone, tablet, or other device you use, such as information about what kind of device you have, and information about the videos you watch. If you contact us with feedback or questions, we may collect your email address so that we can respond to you.

### **How Do We Use Your Information?**

We use your information to allow you to use and enjoy TikTok. For example, we use your username and password to let you access your account. We may use information about what videos you watch to show you additional videos that we think you’ll enjoy. We use information about your device to keep TikTok running smoothly.

### **How Do We Share Your Information?**

We may share your information with companies that provide support to TikTok.

We may share your information to keep you or others safe. We may also share your information to keep TikTok safe, protect our rights, and comply with laws. We don’t sell your information or share it to target ads based on your activity across the services of different businesses.

### **How Do We Keep Your Information Safe?**

We have appropriate security protections to help keep your information safe. These protections help stop others from stealing your information or using it in bad ways. But online security is never perfect, so be careful when using online services.

### **How Long Do We Keep Your Information?**

How long we keep your information depends on several things, such as the type of information and the reason why we collected the information. In general, we only keep your information as long as we need it.

### **What Rights Do You Have?**

You have the right to know, access, correct or delete your information. You can submit a request at [https://www.tiktok.com/legal/report/privacy](https://www.tiktok.com/legal/report/privacy) or by sending your request to the address provided in the “[Contact Us](#contactus)” section below. Depending on where you live, your parent or guardian can also make these requests for you. If you, or your parent or guardian, do make such a request, we will respond appropriately and will not penalize you for it.

### **Do You Ever Update This Privacy Policy?**

Yes, we may update this page from time to time, so please check back.

### **What If I Have Questions or Need More Information?**

For more information, please review the rest of this Privacy Policy with your parent or guardian.

**_For Parents, Guardians, and Other Adults_**
----------------------------------------------

TikTok USDS Joint Venture LLC (“TikTok USDS Joint Venture”, “we” or “us”) is committed to protecting the privacy of children. This Children’s Privacy Policy explains how we collect, use, share, and otherwise process the personal information of users under the age of 13 (“Children” or “Child”) on a separate experience of the TikTok services for Children in the United States (the “Under 13 Experience”).

The Under 13 Experience is designed for Children residing in the United States. It allows Children to engage with TikTok’s fun video features while limiting the information collected from them. Children can view videos from other creators and explore their creativity by capturing their own videos with music and special effects. While Children may save these videos directly to their device, the videos will not be collected by us or viewable by other users. Children also have a more limited interactive experience; for example, they cannot exchange messages with other users, and other users cannot view their profiles.

### **What Information We Collect from Children**

When a Child registers for TikTok, we collect only limited information, including username, password, and birthday.

We may also collect certain information automatically from the Child’s device or network, including internet or other network activity information such as IP address, web browser type and version, country-level location, as well as certain usage information, such as video watched and time in the app.

If a Child reaches out to us via the in-app feedback form, we collect the email address that the Child provides solely for the purpose of responding to the inquiry.

While certain information we collect from children and subsequently use and disclose may constitute sensitive personal information under applicable state privacy laws, we only process such information in order to provide the Under 13 Experience and within other exemptions under applicable law.

### **How We Use Children’s Information**

We use the information we collect to provide and support our services. For example, we use username and password to authenticate Children. We may use the information that is collected automatically to provide personalized content; serve contextual advertising; perform analytics and troubleshoot; protect the security and integrity of the user and our services; and ensure legal and regulatory compliance. We have technical, contractual, and other reasonable controls in place to help ensure persistent identifiers are used for these permitted purposes.

Children cannot publicly share personal information on the Under 13 Experience, including videos or profile information.

We do not engage in profiling which results in legal or similarly significant effects, as defined under applicable law.

### **How We Share Children’s Information**

We may share the information that we collect as permitted by applicable law. Recipients may include affiliates controlled by, or under common control with, TikTok USDS Joint Venture as necessary for the purposes set forth within this Children’s Privacy Policy, and our service providers as necessary for them to support the internal operations of the Under 13 Experience. We may also share the information that we collect including in connection with a sale, merger or other business transfer, and for legal reasons, to enforce our Terms, and to protect our interests and safety, and those of our service providers, business partners, and community.

TikTok does not sell information from Children to third parties and does not share such information with third parties for the purposes of cross-context behavioral advertising.

### **Data Security and Retention**

We make efforts to treat Children’s information securely and in accordance with this policy. Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. Although we take steps to protect this information, we cannot guarantee the security of information transmitted through the TikTok services; any transmission is at the user’s own risk.

We employ technical and organizational measures designed to achieve a level of security appropriate to risks of varying likelihood and severity and that take into account the rights and freedoms of users. We maintain these technical and organizational measures and will amend them from time to time to maintain or improve the overall security of our systems.

We retain Children’s information for as long as reasonably necessary to fulfill the purpose for which the information was collected. The retention periods are different depending on different criteria, such as the type of information and the purposes for which we use the information.

Subject to applicable laws, including Executive Order 14352 and any compliance obligations thereunder, TikTok USDS Joint Venture may transmit Children’s information outside of the United States, including for purposes of sharing with recipients as described in this Children’s Privacy Policy.

### **Your Rights**

A parent or guardian may submit a request to access or delete the information of their Child, as well as a request to appeal a decision we have made about such a request, by contacting us via the webform or the physical address provided in the [Contact Us](#contactus) section below.

Depending on your state of residence, you (as a parent or guardian) may have the ability to exercise certain rights over your Child's account. For example, you may download account data or exercise other rights in connection with your Child by contacting us via the webform or physical address provided in the [Contact Us](#contactus) section below. We will address these requests in accordance with applicable law and subject to proper validation. We will not retaliate against you or your Child for exercising such rights and choices, although some aspects of the Under 13 Experience may no longer be available to your Child.

### **Privacy Policy Updates**

We may update this Privacy Policy from time to time. When we update this Privacy Policy, we will notify you by updating the “Last Updated” date at the top of the new Privacy Policy, posting the new Privacy Policy, or providing any other notice required by applicable law. We recommend that you review this Privacy Policy regularly to stay informed of our privacy practices.

### **Contact Us**

Questions, comments and requests regarding this Privacy Policy should be addressed to:

*   Contact us: [https://www.tiktok.com/legal/report/privacy](https://www.tiktok.com/legal/report/privacy)
*   Mailing Address: TikTok USDS Joint Venture LLC, 5800 Bristol Parkway, Suite 300, Culver City, CA 90230
